We hit a 100 million annual revenue run
rate at 11 months. Groom did it in 22
months, right? And they were acquired
for 1.2 billion. A1 took them 10 years
to hit 100 million. We hit 200 million
run rate in 18 months.
>> All right, Danny, welcome to the show,
man. Why don't we start off? Why don't
you give a little little intro to
yourself? So, who are you? What do you
do?
>> Hey, Sean. Thanks for having me. Quick
background myself. Always been an
entrepreneur. Started working at a very
young age at 15. I was a telemarketer.
So that's how I got started working. Age
24 had my first business was a
restaurant. Did that for three four
years. Then ventured in hotel furniture
business, import export from China into
the US. Eventually work on some big
projects like the MGM city center in
Vegas. Did that also for the three four
years. Then in 2010, I took a leap of
faith and moved to Hong Kong um to
launch a e-commerce company that was
doing group buying. And then when
Groupon went international, they
acquired 51% of my company. Yeah. We
became the largest e-commerce company in
the region. I left in 2014. We're doing
about 200 million annual revenues. I had
a good exit. That's where, you know, I
made my first million. Yeah. Per seion.
Um but and then after e-commerce I was
like hey you know what do I do next? Had
a lot of options at my disposal and I
didn't just want to go back into
e-commerce even though that was the easy
route for me. Um I ventured then I
actually you know got started in
diagnostics and DNA testing. So founded
Prenetics which was a life sciences DNA
testing company. And again this was 2014
right? So very early no one was really
talking about this stuff. And I think
you'll see that in my entrepreneur
career, it wasn't the obvious choice,
but everyone's like now looking back is
obvious choice, right? I mean, think
about in 2010, no one was using
e-commerce in Hong Kong. Yeah. Everyone
in fact told me to go back to US.
They're like, Danny, just go back to US.
This model is not going to work in Hong
Kong. We we made it the number one
e-commerce company at the time. But
going back to Prenetics, you know,
started as a life sciences company. when
COVID hit, you know, we were prime
position to take advantage of it. We
worked very fast. In two weeks, we got
our CO testing kit. We then became Hong
Kong's number one co PCR provider as
well as in the UK. So, those yeah, three
years we Yeah, I would say we were like
printing money, I would say. Right. Um,
>> they exploded.
>> At one point, we're doing 40,000 PCR
tests a day, right? We total did 28
million. This is laboratory PCR test
those three years. We did 700 million
plus revenue. Um in three years time we
listed on the NASDAQ in 2022 where
household name everyone that arrived in
Hong Kong at one point had a mandatory
prenetics PCR test. And then of course
that led goes into you know IM8 which is
kind of you know what happened after
COVID you know we had a billion dollar
valuation during co in 2022 because co
was still going on 18 months later our
market cap hit I think was like 50
million right went from billion plus to
50 million y'all like right you
really know who your friends are at that
point right because at a billion
>> you got a lot of f got a lot of friends
at a billion you and a lot of friends
that are billing
>> when you're down 95%. Uh, okay. The
stock's down 95%. Were the friends also
down 95% or it wasn't so bad?
>> No, I mean the friends wasn't down 95%.
But when you're when you're going up,
everyone wants to be involved, which is
natural to be fair, right? Everyone
wants to be surrounded by winners, but
very few
>> want to be surrounded and associated
when you're going down, right? Because I
think the path
>> to recover is significantly much harder.
I mean we had a few options like you
know what why don't we just close the
business because you have think about
the the background right we I think in
yeah we did you know 272 million revenue
right and basically 40 tests turned to
nothing right so basically you know our
revenue dropped by 95% and and to be
fair I think the market you know
realized that and was rightfully valued
so we thought okay what do do you know
do we close up shop just return capital
to our shareholders um you know do I do
something else I mean of course you I've
been successful as a operator as well as
investor right so a lot of options still
but you know I knew that you know I
still wanted to create something out of
this and also wanted to be very
responsible to the shareholders from
before coincidentally at the same time
as we were thinking what to do you know
I had the opportunity community to meet
with David Beckham. And this was right
at the same time where I was thinking
about getting into the supplement
category. And when I met David, you
know, it wasn't to like pitch him on,
hey, let's get to the supplement
category. We were just having a
conversation about his background, what
he's doing, and he was very intrigued
about my consumer background as well as
my life sciences background. And he was
telling me, you know, about his problem,
him and Victoria's problem about how
even for where they are as individuals
and of course, you know, they have all
these resources available to them,
right? They even found the supplement
category very overwhelming, especially
that when they're traveling, you know,
they just can't maintain that routine of
taking 12, 13, 14, 15 pills and these
capsules and etc. they just yeah don't
do it right and then yeah me as an
entrepreneur like hey I'm sure there's a
better way for that and yeah after you
know three to four months countless
conversations as I'm I'm sure you can
imagine and someone with David's
pedigree and background if something
went wrong it's not no one cares about
Danny it's always going to be hey David
something blew up right so he had to
take
>> significant precautions
And I told David from day one, hey
David, I know you know for the last 30
years there's been so many people
wanting you to do this category and you
reject it. And I told David something
that was surprising to him. I was like
David if we do this together. Yeah. I
don't want you just as ambassador. I
want you as a co-founder but this brand
has to live beyond you. I don't want
this to be another celebrity brand.
>> Yeah. So let's explain what IM8 is,
right? Because that's the current
business. So I am if I go to the website
I see Beckham, I see Giannis, I see Lily
Collins, I see a bunch of famous people
and they're drinking a little red drink
and you know so if you've seen it most
>> most of the supplement category is
green, you guys are red and um it's a
it's some sort of supplement drink,
longevity drink. You got the Beckham
stack on here and can you explain just
in short like you know just real quick
like what what actually is the product
that you sell?
>> Yeah, so we've made the business model
very simple. We came out with our daily
ultimate essentials and it's very
simple, right? It has 90 ingredients,
replaces 16 different supplements in a
powder shet. You mix it with 12 ounces
of water. You just drink it every single
morning and it takes care of your
foundational nutritional needs. So, what
does that mean? All of your
multivitamins,
um, your CoQ10, MSM,
probiotics, prebiotics, postbiotics, and
because normally you would have to take
the equivalent of 16 different
supplements, that will easily cost you
$250 to $300 on a monthly basis. Yeah.
And for us, we're selling at $90 on
monthly basis, this combination, which
also tastes great and you can carry
around with you everywhere.
>> Right. And you guys have been I mean
you're a public company so you're public
about your numbers but you've talked
about your numbers before. Yes.
>> Um this you're only about a year into
this to this product line right?
>> We're only 20 months in. We only
launched December of 24. Right. And you
know now we've been the fastest growing
supplement brand you ever recorded.
>> What does that mean? How how fast are
you growing?
>> We hit 100 million annual revenue run
rate at 11 months. um in this category
wise I mean Kruans did it in 22 months
right and they were acquired for 1.2 2
billion after 3 years. Ag1 took them 10
years to hit 100 million. We hit 200
million run rate in 18 months.
>> So you're at 200 million a year. So
there's two two angles to this, right? I
have my ecom nerd hat cuz that's been in
e-commerce and I can ask you about the
funnel and the kac and all that. Then
there's just like highlevel,
you know, product market fit. when you
hit a pro when a product hits a nerve
and you've you've nailed the
positioning, the branding. You've nailed
something in category and positioning.
Can you talk to me about category and
positioning? Because I think those are
highly underrated and most people are
terrible at that and it's very hard to
recover if you have category and
positioning wrong. You can be the best
at just trying to crank the grind the
funnel, but it just doesn't matter if
you haven't gotten those that the first
first key decision right. Can you talk
to me about category and positioning?
>> Oh, do you see that? I just stepped over
a million-dollar problem, a
million-dollar business idea. And that's
the thing, most people walk by these
million-dollar ideas all the time and
they don't even notice. And so our
friends at Starter Story, they put
together a list of 90 business idea.
Each one is vetted. They're all real
problems, real gaps in the market
because they talk to hundreds of
entrepreneurs and they put together this
amazing stuff that's incredibly well
researched. And so if you want to find a
bunch of amazing business opportunities,
you can get it for free. just scan the
QR code or click the link in the
description.
>> Even before, you know, we got into this
category, everyone told me not to do
this. They're like, "Hey, supplement
category, highly competitive, so many
bad eggs." And and to be fair, I mean, I
can tell this story now is that, you
know, my whole board disagreed with me,
right? They're like, "You you don't know
anything about supplements, Danny." I
It's true, too, right? I haven't got I I
I didn't do anything in this category
before, right? Yeah. It was e-commerce,
selling coupons, DNA testing, running
the lab, all that stuff. Yeah. But also
to be fair, you before any of that, I
never had a background as well too.
[laughter] Right. Yeah. So, but of
course still, you know, the board was
like, you know what? And then we have to
make a of course a commitment with David
Beckham. There was Yeah. It was not a
small commitment. Correct. And then so
they disagreed with me, but you know, I
knew that if we made a great product and
we've nailed the positioning and the
brand, right? And with the support of
DB, you know, this would be a home run.
So I had to really fight you and educate
my board. And again, it's like, hey, you
know what? If I'm wrong, I'm going to
resign. I'm going to, you know, quit,
right? That was that was what that was
my position because it really I needed
to be convinced myself that was this was
the right move. But but what made you
think that this would be the right move?
Because it it is true. Sub category is
crowded, right? Like a lot of people
have a celebrity. Who cares, right? Like
>> correct. And a lot of celebrity brands
fail, right? They're like my board tell
me there's so many there's actually more
failures of celebrity brands if you
think about than actually success cases,
>> right? So what was your take?
>> So my my take wasn't number one,
everything starts with the product,
right? Everything starts with a better
product than what's available in the
market. And I can yeah honestly say yeah
we have the best product in the market
but like you fairly pointed out
consumers may not recognize that right
and then so this is where you from day
one we spend a more time also on the
taste profile because a lot of times
people have the great product blah blah
blah etc but if it doesn't taste good no
one's going to drink it right so I spend
a week at the factories that's every
single day testing like you know 20 30
different flavors until we got that
taste like ah you know But this taste is
good,
>> right? And that wants to drink again.
But those two things, those two also
doesn't, you know, relate to success,
right? So you mentioned the color, the
brand. We wanted this to stand out. We
didn't want to just create another
greens powder, right? Then no one
created a reds powder, right? And then
so I think by default
>> that was interesting to people.
>> Is it red because it's like made of
beets or it's red because you made it
red? Like you know what I mean? Like did
it need to be red or you chose to be
red? It was a natural coincidence that
when we created the formulation, there
was like beats inside. Yeah. The
formulation and this was a natural red
color and then like let's just
let's just go hard on this color. Right.
>> Right. Which then made sense. And then
our packaging, if you look at is a very
big red box, right? It's very premium
the positioning. So I didn't want just
to be another supplement brand. I wanted
to yeah have a really great unboxing
experience. It's bold. the name, you
know, easy to remember, the fonts, the
colors.
>> How'd you come up with the name?
Because, you know, I whenever I
brainstorm company names, you get 500
names. Each one you look at, you're
like, that could be it. And then, you
know, so like if I had written down on
my list of supplement names, I am and
then the number eight. I might have
maybe it would be like, oh, that kind of
flows, but I would have the courage it
takes to pick such a weird name. Where's
that come from? Why? Why? Why that name?
How'd you know? very good in names right
I would say I'm like really good in
names I mean my my e-commerce company is
called you buy I buy right group buying
right with that just the number you then
prinetics was have prevention and
genetics so you have prrenetics
>> right and then of course IM8 it came I
wanted something simple and easy to
remember um and then I am means I am and
then eight if you flip it around means
infinity infinite possibilities right
and I knew at one A will enter China and
the number eight will also work in
China. Right? So there's definitely
>> lucky number of China, right?
>> Number eight me and it's like I am is
like I am healthy, I am strong, I am
powerful, right?
>> So there's a great meaning behind that.
>> Okay. And so you go into this category
now you get your formulation done.
What's the zero to one? So what did that
what did that look like? You just fire
up Facebook ads, Shopify store. Did you
do anything else? Like what what does
zero to one look like? uh 0 to1 again
the formulation part you know I would
say was a result of also getting an
amazing scientific advisory board yeah
on again when I looked into this was
like okay what are all the different
challenges someone can you yeah go at us
and it's like hey just because we have
David Beckham it's not enough and
everyone knows David is not a scientist
right I'm not a scientist right so we
then the next step was recruiting a
world-class scientific advisory board
the likes of Dr. Don Musum from Mayo
Clinic. Um you James Green the former
chief science of NASA, Suzanne Decoda
the director of microbiome at Cedar
Saii. So these individuals we brought
along they all took part in creating
this formulation and that wasn't enough.
And how did you do that by the way?
That's um what you're cold emailing. Is
there a I I actually know there's like a
there's like an agency there's like a
brokerage service. I don't know if you
know this one. There's a brokerage
service
>> between doctors and supplement brands
that literally it's like get a doctor on
your brand. I don't know if you've seen
this. I haven't seen like a very niche
agency some guy has. But what did you
do? You you cold called these people.
You go fly out, meet them, you expect
me. What's happening?
>> I I knew the former chief of science of
NASA prior. Yeah. Yeah. Basically, he
was at NASA for two years. So that was
easy because he knew me, right? And
again, a lot of this relationships is is
built bound trust. And you know for Dr.
Don Mu Salem you I contacted her on
LinkedIn we got on a call and again the
first time we had it she was very
skeptical cuz so many supplement brands
you know reach out to them and again for
especially as if you're a practicing
physician yeah it's also quite rare to
work with a supplement brand especially
if you're let's say with male clinic
really rare
>> right because they have a lot of
restrictions etc etc right so
>> but I think from day one you even I told
Don Yeah, we're we're still working
today very closely is that we need to
prove the science and evidence. Yeah. So
that's why we embarked on a clinical
trial before we launched the brand. We
embarked on third party testing by not
just one organization but by two by
Euroins and NSF certification for sport.
So that means if you're a professional
athlete, you know it's free from 280
banned substances. So, I have a lot of
friends who are in the supplement game
and [clears throat]
in in general when you're in e-commerce,
it's easy to become very skeptical and
very jaded, of course. Um, not because
anybody means poorly, but just because
it's very easy to get something up and
running and put the make put all your
effort into the packaging, maybe even
some into the taste, but ultimately,
>> you know, you're not in the factory and
and you know, and also it's very easy to
have something that might help, but is
is not scientifically proven, right?
Scientifically proven is a very high
bar. And so, I would say there's almost
two two parts of the ledger. There's the
first part which is like are these clean
ingredients and is it made in a clean
factory? That's kind of like trust test
number one. Trust test number two is
what the hell is a postbiotic? What's a
prebiotic? Does any of this stuff
actually matter if I drink this? Does
anything really change in my body? And I
know obviously I'm asking you know the
priest if religion is real. But I I
guess like if I'm a highly logical
rational person, what would be your most
convincing thing you could tell me that
would make me actually believe in
supplements? A lot of supplements out
there don't work and that's the reality
right and I think the best validation of
our product is that doesn't matter who
we have Beckham blah blah blah etc our
business won't be in 20 months can't be
a 20 million 200 million plus business
without recurring subscriptions and that
means the product works as advertised
all right and the best
>> how does someone know that the product
work how does the customer work you'll
feel it and they get and the best way to
energy. What What are you feeling?
>> Better energy recovery. Yeah. Um you
sleep better, your gut. Yeah. Everything
is working better. Yeah. And of course,
a lot of these individuals, these are
CEOs, athletes. I think the best case I
can show you. I mean, I I was surprised
by this email, right? Around last April
or May of 2025,
right? I got an email from Arena
Sabalinka's team, right? co- email into
me, right? They're like, "Hey, you know,
Arena's been on your product for about
three months now via a recommendation
from her nutrition coach. When you're
the world number one tennis player,
every single thing they're measuring
your recovery, how you're feeling three
to four times on a daily basis." And
they don't need a right? I
mean, she has so many options and
resources. And she's like, "Hey, she's
been feeling amazing from a recovery
perspective and she hasn't gotten sick
while on the product. given that they're
traveling, you know, different time
zones every single week, can we partner
together, right? And then so that was a
great validation of the product working
at the highest level of sports. And the
reality is also every single ambassador
that came after that was inbound to me.
>> Hey, let me ask you a question. Is the
market in China or India for that matter
like two big population places? Is the
is the supplement market the same? Is it
just the same but 10 years ago? Um is it
different or what's going on over there?
>> Um India to be honest with you, I don't
know. Um I do know is a much lower price
point and category. Um in China they do
have AG1 but it's not like Yeah, from
what I understand it's not doing well.
>> Why do you think that is? Is it is it
all just price point or is there another
factor? I mean again it goes back you
know to price point education branding
positioning you know there's like so
much right I think to be fair 99% of
American companies go into China and
think they can just succeed with the
same business model um and for China to
operate it successfully you need a
completely different business model
completely different team like for
example my team can't do China 100%
there's like no hell they no way they
can do China, right? So, for me to enter
China, I would need to get a completely
new team of every single individual,
>> right? Tell me about some of the
operational excellence. So, I want to
know what are some things that you're
doing that I could look at that um I
could be inspired by. Oh, that that you
know, the way they do that, that's
really good. So, now I'll give you a
couple examples. So, we had Chad from
Grun's on the podcast and he was showing
us their funnels, their Facebook ads.
were looking at his ad library together
and they were showing like he's got like
you know there's eight different sort of
reasons to buy, right? Maybe you're on
OMIC and you want Ompic support. Maybe
you're looking for mood and here's a
mood thing. Maybe you're a woman and
your hair and your your hair's falling
out postpart whatever. I don't know what
they're I don't remember the exact
angles. He's like I've got like the ad
that goes to the landing page for that
persona for that problem for that sales
pitch and I'm running all eight
simultaneously. Whereas most
entrepreneurs are, you know, usually
just get fixated on one and they don't
get they don't get as much of the
market. He would tell us that or um Eric
Ryan from Method Soap and Ali Gummies
came on and he was he's a master of
packaging and positioning and he said I
was looking in the vitamin aisle and
>> you know first thing I knew was that
every container was round and so we
would be a rectangle and he's like it's
as simple as that. I look for a sea of
sameness and everywhere in the aisle
that I see a sea of sameness I know
there's an opportunity to come in and do
something different. That's what they
did in Band-Aids. and soap and vitamins.
>> Yeah, I would I would say even right
now, you know, to be fair wise, you
know, the ads and landing pages,
personas, that's quite standard
operating procedure right now, right? If
you're a DTC brand doing$100 to $200
million, I mean, you have to be doing
that, Greg. Um, I think for us wise, I
think one thing that we've done really
well was scaling on meta ads. You know,
right now we have anywhere from, you
know, two to three,000 ads live at any
given time. We're testing out you know
500 to 800 creators on a weekly basis.
So it's that constant testing um that is
really really important right and you
have and right now the reality is even
with ad buying I mean you know app
buying is like a commodity right now.
Yeah, before a few years ago, you have
to be really really good at ad buying.
But now Meta does all of that for you
already, right? You don't need to do the
targeting. You don't need to do all this
stuff, right? All you need to really
figure out is how do you get really good
creatives and really good creative
diversity on the different personas
because now you need a creative to do
the targeting. And
>> so tell me about that creative machine.
So you said two things. You said you
have a couple thousand ads running at a
time. So are those like statics or those
videos? statics and videos I would say
is about you know 55 60% statics and
then the rest videos
>> and you're doing that with what a studio
you're doing that with AI what is the
machine that's building all that
>> uh combination of everything so we have
our own ambassadors yeah again we have
of course we have like top 10 very
famous ambassadors then we have another
thousand or more or so ambassadors
affiliates that are creating lots of
content for us on a daily basis right
And that feeds the engine depending on
whichever personas that we're going to.
And a lot of times you have your proven
winners and then it's like how do we
recreate all these proven winners
because you know there's also create a
fatigue that happens right. So we've
have our own create a fatigue score that
we identify. So we know okay when a ad
is potentially going to get in fatigue
which then ultimately will drop that row
right again 300,000 above on a daily
basis on meta you know which is quite
high given that we're only 20 months in
right and we've been able to
>> yeah scale that and I think one key
thing again public information given
we're public companies that if you look
at what happened in Q2 versus Q1 Q1 our
CAC was 305 right our average order
value is about $230, right? So, um, and
we we doubled our marketing spend in Q2,
right? We doubled it from about 17 to
$33 million in a quarter, right? Our CAC
actually went down by $4, right? From
305, 301 because you would imagine if
you're doubling spend, your CAT's always
going to go up. Yeah.
>> Right. And then so I think we reached a
point where again we got the engine
running. The brand is also doing very
well from a brand position and we've ran
now 200 plus offline events. I think
this is something that I haven't seen
any other supplement brand do.
>> And why are you doing that? Because that
creates content or because that creates
loyalty or both? What's the what's the
main reason to do 200 offline events? I
mean it's very important from us from
day one you a this is about a authentic
[snorts] product science and you know
when we have these events we have our
scientific advisory board members there
they're talking about the product right
and again this is not just a marketing
aspect is you know we have real science
behind the brand they get to meet our
formulators and our scientists and
doctors last week in New York we did
like yeah seven events in seven days
right um as part of [clears throat] US
been I always say these the events are
very difficult to scale right
>> but I think that's very very important
especially in the age of AI you don't
know what's real you don't know what's
what's fake or whatever right
>> and then so I think having that offline
presence is really important for us
>> yeah and I think that's pretty counter
to where most brands are right now I
think it's so easy to sit sit at your
laptop fire up ads let you know tweak
your landing page and Clearly, you get
the scale, you get to measure it, you
get every you get the feedback loop
right away. You don't have to like go
get face rejection out in the real
world. And it almost means that like
offline has this disproportionate
premium because it's simply like less
contested. And once you've had an
in-person touch point and then you go
see an ad, right? It's going to be a
completely different experience than if
you've never it's just a
>> brand and I tribute you that CAC
lowering when we double our spend. We're
not talking about like a lot of double a
lot of spend doubling, right? And even
July our cap fell to $239,
right? Yeah. You know, which is, you
know, we're spending more than $10
million a month on marketing, right? And
then so it was continue lower, but I do
believe again I don't have quantifiable
data to say this is all offline, but I'm
going to continue to double down on
offline events um because that's a
really important to the brand side of
things. Tell me about some of the kind
of early days of entrepreneurship where
maybe your entrepreneurial philosophy
got got formed or the core skills that
are helping you today, but where were
they first kind of originated? Where
where'd you cut your teeth doing it?
>> I mean, so I dropped out of high school,
right? So I was, you know, basically a
bad kid. Got kicked out of high school
for fighting. So I had to really learn
everything, you know, on the streets, I
would say, right? as as an entrepreneur,
you you're always faced with making
decisions with very limited information.
And I think, you know, for everyone that
knows me, they know me. I'm like very
street smart, right? I can figure things
out by myself with very little
information.
>> Where where were you going to high
school?
>> In San Francisco.
>> Oh, you were in San Francisco. So, you
get kicked out. So, why telemarketing?
How did you stumble into telemarketing?
>> Um I I mean I think I didn't stumble. I
think it was like what do I do? You
know, I'm not going to school, right?
So, and then as a telemarketer, you
know, I was 15. I was good at it. I was
good in, you know, kind of like co-
calling people.
>> What were you selling?
>> I was selling time shares.
>> Time shares.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Remember time shares is like
again this is about 30 years ago, right?
So those few years where I would say I
was a very bad kid
actually formed a lot of my thinking as
an entrepreneur because I always had to
reinvent myself. always had to go to a
new school, make new friends, um, and
get very comfortable. And yeah, I I I
believe I can survive anywhere. You put
me into Nigeria, Africa, whatever it is,
I will figure it out.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
The Yeah, the sort of more adversity you
face, the more confidence you get um
when you survive. You know, there's
there's another guy um Craig Craig
Clemens who came on the podcast, good
friend, great guy. He's also an
e-commerce sponsor. So his company
Golden Hippo does hundreds of millions a
year in sales. Bootstrapped him and his
brothers. He also was in telemarketing.
He was selling dating products when he
was younger.
>> And um you know he he was sharing for
him one of the ways he got better at
sales was he was going to these seminars
and he was reading books and he was just
looking for like anything he could pull
out one line one one copyrighting thing
one psychological um sort of hook that
he could pull on to. Did you do any of
that or were you just brute force
numbers game? I mean you have to like
communicate you know properly right I
think you always have to be direct and I
think I've always kept that right so
very transparent in terms of hey
especially with be let's say trying to
meet someone for the first time always
telling teams don't don't you know don't
talk about bo right I think you just
have to be direct and transparent
>> what's in it for them what's in it for
us and again for me I've always for each
of my businesses I'm always trying to
deliver greater value first I think
that's very important I never try to
look at what's in it for me. I was like,
what can I help this person with? How
can I help my partner? How can I help
their business? And that's been my
philosophy from day one. I think if you
have that type of philosophy going in,
it doesn't matter if the other partner
doesn't reciprocate. You move and you
learn and move on.
>> Mhm. So, you're telemarketing. You learn
about the numbers game. You learn that
you got to sort of figure it out. You
get street smart to figure out things to
survive.
>> And you and you you learn it doesn't
matter who you talk to, right? You can I
can go up to anyone. And it's just
basically you the worst thing that
happens is they reject me, right?
>> How many people would you call in a day?
>> It was like night shift at the time when
I was working. So it's like you know
6:30 then I would say 100 200 people.
>> And of that what's the rejection rate
still going to be like 90 90 95%. Right.
[laughter]
And and so was that something did you
have to sort of what did you tell
yourself to be able to like kind of
quickly bounce back from that?
>> No, you just I mean again it's a it's a
numbers game. You just fail, you know,
but basically you just tell yourself,
hey, you know, the next one is going to
be more likely to be positive, right? So
you have just get through it. And I
think you know to be fair, telemarketing
taught me a lot. Yeah. You have to have
a thick skin. Even when you talk to
investors, same thing, right? when
you're early on they getting investment.
I mean you talk to 100 investors you
only five may invest in you. So there's
nothing different about that. It's just
you're not getting rejected like hanging
up on you but you you're still faced
with that. Right? I mean give you an
example um of how that came to use right
furniture business. I was co- calling
basically MGM then I got a meeting and
then I was able to get a meeting that
was able to you know deliver the value I
was able to get but without my co-
calling days I probably wouldn't have
done that right even when I did my
e-commerce business you buy I buy which
was group buying I remember I went to
Hong Kong and I had to co- call all the
merchants myself right because again
this is not like you know
>> starts off with nobody
>> yeah it starts with nobody right so I
remember one time I was calling a big
restaurant group and then director of
marketing He hung up on me and I was
like he hung up on me really like he
like was like hurt me. I was like, "Wow,
this guy like he said some like very bad
words and blah blah blah to me, right?"
And then normally I was like, "Oh
you probably like, you know, I was
thinking, wow, who's this guy's boss?" I
was thinking, right? And then I then I
like found who this B guy's boss is. He
was director of marketing and I co-
called the office and it was Sandeep and
he owned like 30 plus restaurants, this
Indian entrepreneur. And I asked for
Sandeep, called the front desk. He
picked up the phone and I'm like, "Hey,
this is Danny. I just moved to Hong
Kong. I moved here from the US. Yeah.
Can have five minutes of your time
because I have this interesting
e-commerce idea and would love to see if
I can partner with you. Right. And then
he met with me the next day for 20
minutes and he told me, "Danny, hey, um,
Danny, I don't think your business is
going to work in Hong Kong because why
would I give 50% off to customers and I
only get 25% of the check, right?" But
you know what? because you know, you
called me after my director of marketing
hung up on you and we're still here. I'm
going to work with you and give you all
of my dirty restaurants and sign you up.
Um, and he did that because he knew, you
know, I didn't give up and just was
persistent, resilient, and that changed
the trajectory of the business because
he gave me 30 restaurants and I needed
one deal a day, right? So, he gave me
basically my whole next 30 days was
filled by one guy saying yes. And of
course then I can continue but he was a
big restaurant group right it was a very
and then I would then go to other
restaurant groups because got him
because he was so famous you know Sandep
Donnie Khan was working with us yeah can
you partner too then yeah and once you
once you get yeah some traction etc then
more and more people work with you right
but that's just reality someone has to
give you a chance and you just always
have to be on the hunt
>> my my uncle Vinnie was a doortodoor when
he came to the country he came to this
country he was doortodoor salesman of
like the Bible or I don't know what he
was selling. And I asked him the same
thing. I'm like, "Man, you were walking
around in the heat in Georgia in the
summers. You're walking house to house,
knocking on door, like getting rejected
even more than on the phone, like to
your face, door slam."
>> And um same thing, 90 to 95% of people
door slam us. He was the top sales guy.
And he he had a thick Indian accent. I
was like, "How did you do that?" And he
goes, "Oh, I took rejection better than
anyone else." I said, "Well, how did you
take rejection better?" He goes, "I put
a price on the word no." So he said, "If
a if a yes is worth $100 to me and it's
going to take me, you know, for every 20
nos, I get one yes."
>> Then he's like, "Then every no is worth
$5 to me, right?" He's like, "I just" So
when they would say no, I would hear in
my head, "All right, that's five bucks
in the bank. Let's keep going." And so
he's like, "I was adding up the nos. I
was putting a price on it cuz I knew
really like it's a numbers game. I have
to keep knocking." And so I have to like
sort of see each knock as a success even
though what I my ears hear is is a
rejection. I have to change what I'm
hearing. And that led him to be the
number one sales guy in the country. And
he ended up training all the other sales
guys. And I think there's a I think
there's something everybody should take
from from that whether you're
fundraising or whatever whatever you're
doing that like you know e-commerce I
think a good like I if I looked at our
conversion rate right now I think it's
like 2 point something percent. 2% 2 and
a half% maybe. You know, 97.5%
of people come to our site and say,
"Hell no."
>> Now, you don't feel it as much when it's
e-commerce, but but you but but you feel
it when it's over there, you know? So,
so it's all a numbers game.
>> Mhm.
>> Yes.
>> What else? You mentioned MGM. What's
What's the story there? I didn't
understand that one.
>> When I started first working in the
hotel furniture business, I was doing
hotels that were like 50 rooms, you 100
room, small hotels, right? how small
hotel chains just doing all of their
custom furniture.
>> Sorry, can you go back? Why why do why
does Danny start selling hotel
furniture? How does that happen?
>> No, because I was doing my restaurant
business at the time. I had a good
friend that was an interior designer and
she was just telling me, hey, you know,
she's a designer for these hotels and
she was having difficulty sourcing
furniture. And I was like, why don't you
look in China? And she's like, she
doesn't know how to. And then I'm like,
why don't I help you? And then she's
like, okay, why don't you help me,
right? And I just did it for her. And
then but after a few of the hotels I
figured out you know it's the same
process if I make 50 chairs or 50 tables
as if I make two to 3,000 chairs right
so I was like who is making 2,000 hotel
rooms right now and at that time was
like Vegas right then I started co-
calling the Vegas hotels and eventually
I co- called MGM and she gave me a
meeting and then I went into the meeting
and you know one year later I got a you
know $4 million contract with MGM.
>> How did that feel that first kind of big
contract?
>> I mean, it felt, you know, amazing. But
of course, ultimately, you know, I
wanted to deliver and that's so that's
why a lot of times even when we do an
achievement or milestone, you know, I
always tell the team, hey, you know,
this is good, you know, but it's not the
end, right? We're just getting started,
right? And it's like, you know, even
last month, we hit 20 million in monthly
revenue, right? But hey, this is good
prog, great progress, I would say. But
we have so much care opportunity. So,
but you know, I was of course happy that
we're able to get such a big customer.
>> When you were doing the COVID testing,
you were kind of in the right place when
COVID hit where you could provide
testing. You said a couple interesting
things. One, the ramp was crazy. You
said you did like 700 million revenue in
the couple of years, which is just a
bonkers number. I'm sure there was a lot
of free cash flow in that, too, not just
revenue. Yeah, we made over $100 million
net.
>> Net. Yeah, exactly. And and you The
second thing was you said like in Hong
Kong like everybody who entered the
country had that sounds like maybe you
had like a kind of a really valuable key
contract that you won or some sort of
like a you know pretty defensible
position. So can you tell the the story
of that? And also during that, did you
did you think did you know well this the
music's going to stop on this at some
point and what happens after that or did
you say I don't know let's just run and
we'll figure it out when we when when
that happens.
>> Yeah. So I can tell you the backstory on
this. Right. So um I think this is in
April. Yeah. April of 2020. So CO was
getting very bad. I had a meeting with
the chief executive of Hong Kong. I was
like, hey, you know, we have a lab, you
know, CO seems to be getting, you know,
worse and worse, you know, by the day.
Yeah. Can we somehow provide support and
make use of our laboratory? Yeah. To
basically provide COVID testing to the
community, right? Um and then, you know,
the chief executive said the same at the
time said, you know what, um you know,
we have our own public health
laboratory.
We can do it all of ourselves. So that
was that right and I'm like okay no no
no worries stand because at the time
wise it was very difficult to get a
COVID test in Hong Kong. you would have
to go to the hospital and they were
charging like $300 to $400 USD for a
COVID test and then I knew the cost of a
COVID test is a fraction of that, right?
And they were making so much money and
at that time you don't want to go to a
hospital to do a COVID test because it
means that you may get infected too,
right? I was like, you know what, we'll
just create our own at home PCR test.
And then so we launched that within
about a little bit more than two weeks
and every day we're just trying to help
out the community. were selling it for
$100 US when everyone was selling it for
$400. And even the hospitals would call
me like why are you guys selling it for
so cheap, right? I was like I was like I
just want to help the community, right?
That was that was the core um reason for
getting into here. So every single day
we'll be selling out. And then July,
yeah, the government actually then again
called me and like can we meet again cuz
it was getting out of control, right?
you know, three months later and they're
like, "Daniel, we need your help. Um,
yeah, can you help us service
COVID testing to the community?" I'm
like, "Yeah, we love to help." Like,
yeah, uh, what do you want us to do?
They're like, "We want you to test
300,000
restaurant workers across 18,000
restaurants in Hong Kong."
And I'm like,
"How long of a time do you want this
testing?" They're like, "Yeah, we want
you to do this in 3 weeks." So, that was
a crazy operations, right? I don't know
why I I even said yes to it. Again, we
went from 100,000 100 200 tests on a
daily basis to now testing, you know,
300,000 people in about a month time,
which basically meant that we had to
scale up from 200 tests to 10,000 tests
on a daily basis. and myself, my
executive team where we're were all in
the whole we then we h you and there
were so many people without jobs at that
time, right? And then basically we
started mass hiring. Yeah. At one point
we had like two to three,000 people.
>> What was the bottleneck? Was it the
actual tests the supply chain for the
test or was it the people in the lab to
read the test? Cuz you you get the
result at home, right? What you
>> No, no, you get the result in the lab.
>> Okay. So you would send it in.
>> You have to send it in. Um this this was
before antigen tests were rolled out,
right? Because very early on you had do
the you had to do a laboratory test
which is the PCR test and then the
antigen test which is the quick ones
which are less accurate only came into
play you know maybe one year after.
>> I see. I see. Okay. So, so you said
supply chain and hiring people,
>> people, logistics, data, right? And then
we're the first company contracted by
the Hong Kong government to do mass
community testing. And of course, you
know, 6 months later, we there was like
14 15 different laboratories
that were also doing COVID testing.
However, the thing that stood out from
us is I think a lot of it has to do with
my technology and e-commerce background
and and data and all that stuff. Yeah.
was um we were the only testing provider
that never had a upup when it came to
false positives and false negatives. And
then so when all these other
laboratories they messed up and then the
government got a lot of yeah crap for it
right obviously because if you get a
positive during that time you have to go
to detention for like seven to 14 days
right and then so this is why at one
point every single individual that
landed Hong Kong airport was mandated a
prenetics test because they wanted to be
the most secure and most accurate test.
Did you have to do anything crazy to
unlock the supply chain there
>> on a daily basis? You had to be
fighting, you know, with so many
different other, you know, laboratories
around the world, right? You to get all
this supply chain. So, it was a every
single day we're fighting and again a
lot of times, you just to outbid them
and we had volumes, right? So, again,
but it was a constant battle. Those were
some crazy two, three years of
craziness.
>> Yeah. When you So, I I my last question,
you know, I had a few friends who were
doing this. I had one friend who was
doing mobile testing. He had like vans
that were testing. I had another friend
that was doing PPE when when you
couldn't get masks and and other PPE to
hospitals and whatnot.
>> And people were making money handover
fist and doing this cuz there's so much
I mean it was the strongest demand I've
ever seen for anything ever, right? Like
life or death at global scale. But you
know some of those people they kind of
stashed away enough cash that it was
still a success and some people had
overbuilt and then suddenly the music
stopped and now it's like a lot of work
for nothing. So every so give me an
example right on on that exact thing is
that it was it was right when we knew CO
was over I let go of 2,000 people very
very fast and that turned out to be a
really you know good decision you know
because again during that time wise and
you had Q health uh you had you know
Lucera and these were at the time they
were listed companies at one point Q
health was $3 billion market cap they
had a billion dollars in revenue in the
US right Luca they had another like I
think they $2 billion market cap. Yeah.
They went bankrupt, you know, 18 months
after COVID because they overbuilt. They
built their own manufacturing places.
They bought into the athome testing
which never panned out postco.
But I knew that for both sides, for a
company to survive after this, we needed
to make a drastic cut. And also for the
individuals, right? Because what what
are we gonna do? Why am I have 2,000
people if there's no testing? I'm just
gonna like right you stand around which
is not good for them. Everyone has to
move on you know with their life and and
livelihood and you know that was very
difficult decision of course but
ultimately it was the right decision for
both sides.
>> If you were I don't know if you know you
meet a lot of entrepreneurs or you know
there's a lot of people that will come
up to you that are you excited about
what you've done and they're trying to
do something and they're pitching you an
idea. What do you think most
entrepreneurs just don't get? What's the
one thing if you feel like you could
just shake them and and say, "Look, Ben,
you just really don't get it." It's the
gap between where you are and where you
want to be is this. What do you think
that gap looks like for most people?
>> I think I mean, again, about going back
to number one, right? You know, I always
believe that if you build the best
product in the market, it just makes
everything so much easier, right? And
[clears throat] I think if you look at
again, even you when the co testing, I I
we had the best product in the market.
So if you have the best product in the
market, it's much easier to build
foundation, branding, positioning,
premium pricing over any of your
competitors, right? And I also believe,
you know, as entrepreneurs, etc., you
have to get into the weed of everything.
I think some entrepreneurs, they don't
like to, you know, get involved in every
part of the business, but at least from
my perspective, you know, what's worked
very well for me is I'm involved in
every part of the business. Doesn't
matter if we're a hundred million
company, 200 million, we'll be in a
billion dollars, whatever. I guarantee
I'll be involved in a lot of the key all
the key decisions. Um because I think
that's what separates a founder from a
higher CEO, right? I think the founder
and that's why a lot of times these
founders blah blah blah etc. they grow
their business to 400, they hire CEO.
Often times the founder always comes
back, right? Because the CEO
perspective, they're always much more
conservative and they're looking at this
from a paycheck where the founders were
able to take risks that a CEO wouldn't
be able to take. So for example, even
when I started IM8, if it was a CEO,
there was no way he would have been able
to take that risk, right? But because
I'm the founder, you have so much at
stake here. There's no one in the
organization that to take a risk as much
as me,
>> right? To be able to make that move.
Let's get into the supplement category,
right? Yeah, it's I don't know if you've
read Have you read founder mode the sort
of Paul Graham blog post?
>> Yeah, I mean I've read the Yes, correct.
I think founder mode is very different
correct is like yeah we we see things
very very uniquely different. I think
entrepreneurs you know really have to
dive into that.
>> Yeah. And you know the first thing you
said about product you know build the
best product in the market. I mean on
one hand that sounds obvious um of like
oh well okay yeah and I would say most
people everyone thinks they have a good
product. Yeah, but you have the
realistic, right? It's like it's like a
big difference. I I tell people, how do
you know? I like don't trust me. Just
put it into cloud. Put in attach. What's
better? I know AG1 Doran Grun, right?
Let's see what it says on the similar
product.
>> Right. [laughter]
>> What does it say? Let's try it.
>> Yeah.
>> Says if I had to choose one today, I'd
buy IM8 over AG1. So you there you go.
It says it's not just 90 ingredients
versus 75 cuz that's ingredient count is
mostly marketing.
>> Okay. I think that it's currently doing
a better job putting useful ingredients
at disclosed non-trivial doses in the
same daily drink. And then it goes
through the formula and it gives gives a
little bit of an answer. So at least
according to to Chad GPD right now that
that is that is correct which I think is
>> okay I'm cut I'm going to cut that
segment out and use it as an ad. Okay,
that's perfect. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Give me my kickback and then
you can do whatever you want.
>> Yeah. Give me 10% back.
>> I'll be one of your TikTok affiliates.
>> Yeah, exactly. Affiliates. Yeah. You
know, I sold my company to this guy,
Mike, um, Mike Whitmire, and he was
telling he had built the number one
ranked result for buying or selling gold
online. So, anybody wants to buy gold?
His company was was the the premier
leader. And I was excited when we sold
cuz I was like, "Oh, you know, so much
about SEO. What are all the SEO hacks
that we we're not doing? I'm I I'm
terrible at SEO. I've never even tried
that as a growth strategy." So, I was
like, "Tell me tell me like, you know,
what should we start doing?"
And after a few meetings, I was like,
"Dude, when are you going to tell me
like the hacks?" And he's like, "Well,
there's some best practices." He's like,
"There's not really hacks." He's like,
"So I was like, "What'd you do with the
gold company?" And he goes, "I printed
out like the page, the web page for all
of us." And I asked myself honestly, "Is
there a reason you should use us? Why
should Google put us number one? Are we
better? Are we actually better? Is it
easier to use? Is it Is it easier to
understand? Is it more friendly? Is it
faster? like, "Do we have are we better
in any way?" And he's like, we had a
cold honest conversation with ourselves
that no, we were not better. And then we
decided, well, we actually have to be
better if Google's going to rank us
higher. And slowly but surely, we did,
you know, one brick by brick, we just
made the actual experience better until
we felt we actually deserve to be number
one. And guess what? Like at that point,
we didn't need any of the hacks. We
actually were number one. And I just
remember thinking like, oh, I feel like
you just taught me like a very valuable
um like, you know, a very valuable
obvious lesson that I needed to hear
from someone like you. I needed to hear
from the guy who could shatter this myth
in my head that the guys who ran number
one are always just doing these clever
tricks. And it's like there's no trick.
The trick is be the best. And if you're
not willing to be the best, like if you
know there's no way around. You just got
to go through this. And uh I I needed to
hear that at the time.
>> Again, that's that it starts with the
product and I think entrepreneurs that
have to be realistic, right?
>> Well, isn't it right that as a founder,
you basically have to alternate between
delusion and realism
>> in a way that doesn't make any sense.
One in one moment you're going to have
to be delusional. You're going to have
no evidence, but you're going to have to
have the faith. Yes. And you're going to
have to believe even though you have no
experience in this. The market tells you
one thing, smart people tell you one
thing, but you believe another. That's
delusion. And you got to be a little
dulu. But then exactly
>> then you have to switch gears to be
hyper realistic. And the guys, you know,
somebody who's never delusional, they
end up being an employee.
>> And somebody who's only delusional ends
up being a failed founder.
>> It's the person who's able to shift
gears between the two and know when
you're when you need to be in each mode.
That's sort of the art of the whole
thing.
>> Yeah. And and like again I had to be
very like you said I had to be very
delusional because I knew in my head if
we put all these pieces together we
would have a big success right but again
going back I didn't have any experience
in this so you had to build this with
the limited information I knew at the
time.
>> Yeah. Um well Danny I appreciate you
coming on man. This is a you have a fun
story from telemarketing to now uh
running one of the fastest growing
supplement brands in the world and uh
thanks for coming on.
>> Thank you.